you stop?
Dreaming on!
Oh, I get it now.
You're gonna turn into your Sulong form
and go berserk once you gaze at the moon.
It's Jack!
You put together a hell
of a plan, didn't you?
But that doesn't mean
you're strong enough to win.
Just that we were careless.
You won't lay another finger on Kaido.
I'm about to die the snow
red with your blood! Yeah!
Hold your swords. One moment.
Jack devastated our thousand-year-old
kingdom and tormented our people.
That man is our sworn enemy.
We turned him away countless
times, but he would not relent.
The warrior you were
searching for is right here!
It is I!
Race...
I owe the Minx my life!
Every cruelty you committed shall be
punished with the force of my fury!
Please allow us to save
your power for Kaido.
You Karoo as well.
All right, then best of luck.
I'm grateful.
I promise you, Karoo, that I will
show Kaido every ounce of my strength.
Uh!
Ah!
Don't worry.
They can't maintain that for over long.
Yeah, bring it on.
We're Beast 2, you know.
they must have started fighting you think
that rat master jack went
outside with them too
Unlike you, he's
considerate enough to leave.
Excuse me. What was that?
If you've got a problem with
me, just say some, punk ass.
Shinobu?
Ripe, ripe.
Enticement jutsu.
Steady now.
No!
No! Oh, no!
Your plan was solid in theory, but the
execution was lacking, to say the least.
Oh!
Shinobu!
Shinobu! Oh no!
Lord Momonosuke!
I passed out for a moment.
Now, away!
Wait, what?
Oh, how the hell is he flying?
And why is he so bad at it?
I'm too high up!
It's scary!
He's floating through the air.
What sorcery is this?
On behalf of the commander,
I shall execute you.
I can't see a damn thing!
How's he doin' that?
I got it all!
Just in time!
It's Soji!
Let's go!
Hand over the boy.
He and the Kozuki-nei must be erased
from this world once and for all.
Don't worry, I've got you, my lord.
Hey, Momo, nice speech earlier.
You were badass.
Scar, hear me now!
I shall become the Shugen
of the Land of Plano!
I did my best.
All right, Shinobu.
Keep him safe. Understood.
Scar, I shall repay you! Look!
Lord Momonosuke's been saved!
You're not going anywhere.
Acceleration device!
Stealth mode!
Shooting star, shoulder kick!
Ahhhhhhhh!
I'm ready.
Ahhhhhhh!
Ahhhhh!
Whoa, whoa, whoa!
Hold up, my guy!
I can't feel a losing end here.
Knock it off!
Huh?
Damn it, you bird bastard!
You're gonna leave a gigantic hole
in my torso if you keep this up!
And more than just that,
I'll rip you in two.
If you're so scared, why
don't you disappear again?
This might be hard for your bird brain
to comprehend, but it's just a trick!
Let me go, damn it!
Say goodbye. Ah!
Sanji, no!
That attack was crazy.
I think Sanji needs my help.
Hey, Yamato, be back in a sec.
Keep an eye on Momo for me.
Is that okay?
Why wouldn't it be okay?
Uh, right.
You have a point. He...
he is my son after all.
Then hurry it up.
Yeah, leave it to me.
That boy will be protected because
that's what good parents do.
Hey, I'm not done with you.
Wait for me, Momonosuke.
Your father is on his way.
Wait, stop running away from me.
Not so fast, you.
Mama, come on out and help Mama.
The sooner we get rid of these samurai,
the sooner the feast can begin.
You guys want that, don't you?
It's time to pay.
Remember the wedding, the tea
party, and now this banquet?
You've managed to destroy
everything I've looked forward to.
I am going to destroy you
in a spectacular fashion.
You will die.
Like the worm you are!
Eat cocoa!
No!
What the hell was that?
That crone is too
powerful for her own good.
From the stories I've heard, she's
not someone we should take lightly.
She's a pirate captain every
bit as fearsome as Kaido.
Seriously?
But if we can't handle one guy, how are
we supposed to handle two of them, huh?
Come on, I need to ditch her
so I can help Momo and Sanji.
If I go to them, she'll follow.
And the last thing I want to
do is put them in more danger!
Oh, Nish, you're rather
slippery, aren't you?
You're scurrying right out of the way!
Oh, Zeus!
Hey, Zeus!
Where are you?
Get back here! Time to go!
Oh, please tell me, what are you doing?
Do you see firsthand how bad Mama can get?
She's gonna murder us!
I'll have to punish you.
Now, let's get this thing over with.
Yes, Mama.
Hey!
Do you want to escape with your life?
Or have Big Mom kill you?
No, but I can't go against Big Mom.
That is enough!
Give him back, you little cat burglar!
Please find it in your
heart to forgive me.
It's all my fault.
I really messed up, Mama.
I should have never disobeyed you.
Honey, it's all right.
Come back home.
You can make it up to me by
taking out this little tramp.
It's the only way you can earn my trust.
I will do anything for you, just say it.
You want me to cut ties
with the earth's a Noodle?
That's what I like to hear.
Now go and make your mama proud.
Dun-dun-dun-dun!
The time it's blown away!
I'm like the wind!
Dun-dun!
You've only got one
chance to make this right.
If you screw this up, you're done for!
Soul sensor, activate.
I am really sorry, Nami.
I must know to you at home.
You pathetic little coward!
I am so over you!
My, my, my, my, my!
Nobody help me!
My brother, I'm by his side.
Like a bird we will fly.
Saying goodbye.
Soaring so high.
You'll hear our cry.
I'm a tough guy.
Born to be free.
Go go break.
Keep.
Oh!
Ray, Ray, go away.
Whoops!
I think I hit something back there.
No biggie.
As long as it wasn't a pretty flower.
Thanks, Big Bro!
Mama, wake up!
They're doomed!
This is about to get
out of Queen real fast!
He hit her straight in the face!
She's gonna flip out!
Big Bro!
Thank you.
You're the best.
Hey, are you Tia okay?
That was crazy.
Yeah, it was crazy awesome.
Frankie's here.
We got this under control.
Forward!
Show him what you got.
Guess we missed the kickoff.
Oh, boy.
That was quite the entrance they made,
but I have a plan. Can you help out?
Of course.
This should be fun.
Wow, nice!
Looks like they've got
things covered for now.
All right, up I go.
Time to help Keenum on.
I'm ready!
There you are!
I'm so glad I found you!
Kozuki Momonosuke!
And who are you?
Hey, Shinobu!
Don't worry, he's our friend!
He's gonna help you guys out!
An ally?
It's safer to be with him
than be by yourselves.
See ya!
You're a friend of Sir Luffy?
I am.
Well, good.
Then I'll trust you.
What is your name?
My name is Kozuki Oden!
And I shall protect you!
You're my father?
Lord Oden!
And I shall protect you! You're my father?
Hold on, you have breasts and horns,
why you're not my father at all!
This is highly suspicious,
you must be our foe! What?
Smoke escape jutsu!
Wait, why are you running away?
There's too many of them.
We just keep getting bogged down.
Yes, you're right.
There's no point in
fighting these small fries.
We need a change of plans.
What about the Toby Ropal?
Those dinosaur people
that Denjiro mentioned.
Might turn the tide if we
could kill some of them.
Maybe that's a bit optimistic.
But even if we can't win.
We can still stall them.
Oh, you brutes.
It takes some nerve to run me over.
Big Mom is about to go berserk. Look
at
all the
Straw Hats lining up.
Are you ready to get crushed?
Hello, Soul King.
It's been quite a while.
If nothing else, I applaud your captain
for gathering so many unique creatures.
Yo-ho-ho!
I see you're a woman of taste.
Yeah?
You like my iron body, old hag?
All right.
Then I'll give you a demonstration!
Cyborg power!
Can't you dig it?
I'm one of a kind, baby!
Franky, stop!
Are you crazy?
She's an emperor!
We gotta run!
Is that so?
Do we run from emperors?
I don't know.
Guess we could.
But what about our captain?
You want him to become
king of the pirates?
Don't you, Nami?
Yikes, they're huge!
What in the world are they?
Hey! Buzz up!
If you're gonna go wild, stay
in your own banquet hall!
Stupid numbers!
No!
They're as big as the horse!
They're monsters!
Ew!
I'm getting mad flashbacks
from Thriller Park.
Ma-ma-ma-ma.
Fancy that.
Those must be Caesar's failed
attempts at recreating ancient giants.
No use to me, but it would
seem that Kaido loses them.
How lovely.
Is he grabbing what I think he's grabbing?
The Brachio tank!
Who's stopping Chopper in there?
Hey, Monster Face, put that down!
or I'm gonna make you.
Franky.
Radical.
Me. I'm free!
Sucker!
Now that my lasers are
upgraded, I'm unstoppable.
You should have saved that attack for me.
It's too late now, Iron Man.
Your hand, madam.
Fish Man Jiu-Jitsu!
Mill floor!
Whirlpool!
Shoulder throw!
And Ophidium!
So huge, isn't they?
I haven't forgotten what
you think of my fleet.
I'll kill you, too, so it is obvious!
Ha!
Good luck!
Nice plan.
Ha!
Went better than expected.
She'll be even angrier when she gets back.
You are quite a remarkable woman.
Good job!
Thanks for the assist.
I could have been scrap metal.
Then I'm glad we made it in time.
And now...
the moment you've all been waiting for.
Commander Chopper!
Got a status report for me?
Oh, stop! Wake up! Oh, stop!
Put it together!
We're getting a call from Franky!
Come on! Hey! What
gives? You good in there?
Yep, couldn't feel better
thanks to the Racco tank.
You remember our promise, right?
Our promise?
We were gonna combine!
The Iron Pirate, bro!
Docking time, baby!
I...
Pirate?
Finally! Woo-hoo!
Good, I can see the sky.
Okay, I think I can make it up from here.
Not so fast!
Oh, Master Queen! Go away!
I'm taking a break.
But it's Straw Hat!
Uh-oh.
What?! He's here?!
And who the hell is that?!
Hey there, Zoro!
Well, look who it is!
Where are you headed?
Up to Psycheidus!
I'm coming with you.
You're not getting away!
What the hell is that thing? It's huge!
Ready?
Kum Kum Rocket!
Good! We got this!
You said Kaino's up there?
Yeah, I think he's started fighting
with Kinemon's group already!
Just a little more!
Damn!
You ain't gone nowhere on my way!
Give up.
I control these skies.
We're never going to make it
with these bastards hounding us.
I just think they'd be guarding the roof!
Yeah, that's what I'm talking about!
Let's do it!
Ducking formation!
Ready to combine!
Black Rino's standing by!
Crack your head, activate!
Let's do this!
Sorry, bros!
It's only got one seat!
What?!
This is a betrayal!
Who's that up there?
It's Usohachi and Chaparibon!
Are you two all right?
Back to the pleasure hall.
You guys really stuck
your necks out for us.
We really owe you one. Yeah, sure.
But you can thank us later. Yeah, later!
Right now, there's a robot
that you've gotta see! E-poo!
Iron Pirate: General Franky.
Let's rock!
Franky Ken.
Why do you have a giant robot?
Come on
He took out Chalky fast, but
there's bad news. Let's move.
We'll just get stopped.
Oh, yeah
I hope he got away.
I hate to say it, but this suit is tough
Oh sorry.
This just tickles my funny bone.
Look around us.
We're outnumbered.
Enemies on every side.
And yet, for some reason, I
feel like we can't be beat.
You're damn right.
I thought the same thing.
I wonder why.
Where does this courage come from?
When you put it that way,
I suppose we have Mr.
Straw Hat to thank, don't we?
Looks like I won't be able
to jump up there after all.
I guess I need a new plan.
I've got your back, Captain.
You've got me.
Let's head up.
This is a damn pain.
Bastards were ready.
They got the whole swarm up there.
They'll be nothing but caterpillars.
Once we tear off their wings.
I get the sentiment, but do you
have to be so creepy about it?
I suppose those dinosaurs are
the fabled lead performers.
They look pretty tough, but I'm not
worried because our captain's stronger.
That's right.
And as Navigator, it's my duty to
help him get wherever he needs to go.
Don't sweat a thing, brother!
General Frankie's gonna clear out
those thugs before you can say super!
Everyone's ready, Captain.
Right!
Time for round two!
Let's do it!
Samurai!
Don't give them an inch!
We're counting on you!
You better get ready, Kaido!
I'm coming for you!